http://www.newarkgolfclub.co.uk/privacy-policy1

Site Index
Coaching Beginners Guide!
Privacy Policy
Newark Golf Club 'We' are committed to safeguarding the privacy of this website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.
(1) What information do we collect? We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:(a) Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views(b) Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including email address)(c) Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to this website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including email address)(d) Any other information that you choose to send to us.
Cookies
A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We may send a cookie which may be stored on your computer's hard drive. This cookie is only set if you choose to allow your computer to remember your Members Area access details.
Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
Below is a table of cookies used on this site. Not all cookies may be used on all pages as it depends on the specific page content.
Use
Cookie Name
Description
Session information
evou6b8pt
webfxtab_resourcesPane
webfxtab_documentPane
webfxtab_settingsPane
modx_remember_manager
These cookies are used by the Content Management System and are required for the system to function correctly. These cookies identify your unique session on the website. Typically used to maintain the integrity of your session while transacting information with a website.
Cookie Control
DisplayDivasCookiesBanner
This cookie is set in order to remember preferences in regards to cookies.
Google Analytics
_ga
_gat_gat_gtag_UA_149016349_1
_gid
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to monitor traffic levels, search queries and visits to this website. Google Analytics stores IP address anonymously on its servers in the US, your IP address is not associated with any personally identifiable information. These cookies enable Google to determine whether you are a return visitor to the site, and to track the pages that you visit during your session.
Click here for more information about the cookies used by Google Analytics.
Twitter Feed
guest_id
_twitter_sess
ct0
external_referer
personalization_id
If a website page has a Twitter feed widget embedded then these cookies are added by Twitter to control the widget.
Click here for more information about the cookies used by Twitter.
You may change your website browser settings to reject cookies. To learn how to disable cookies or opt out of their usage please visit www.aboutcookies.org.  Please note, however, that some cookies are essential in order to use all functionality on the Website and in the event you do reject cookies this may impair the functionality of the Website.
Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. We may use your personal information to:
(a) Administer the website(b) Improve your browsing experience by personalising the website(c) Enable your use of the services available on the website(d) Send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications(e) Send you email notifications which you have specifically requested(f) Send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications (relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties) which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by emailing us.(g) Provide third parties with statistical information about our users - but this information will not be used to identify any individual user (h) Deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website. We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
Other disclosures
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:
(a) To the extent that we are required to do so by law(b) In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings(c) In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)(d) To the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
International data transfers
Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy. If you are in the European Union, information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union. You expressly agree to such transfers.
Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.
Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)
Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected, updated or deleted.
Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please email our Data Protection Officer
Contact: Simon CollingwoodEmail:manager@newarkgolfclub.co.ukPhone:01636 626282 option 4
